royalty-free
If whatever parts are under warranty, how
can we get them,
what is its online process, how do we
fill the form, where do we have to go, what do we have to do,
I am going to explain all these things in today's video,
so stay tuned to the video,
let's start the video, first of all
you will have to understand some important notes here, in
which what things
are covered and what are not, all these things have been
written for you in the important notes,
I will give it to you in the description,
you can read from there also, but I will
explain some highlight points to you here,
like once the claim is approved, the
defective product will be reversed and picked
up, if once your claim is approved, then at that
time your product will be
picked up and a replacement will be installed in its place,
you should know these things first
and the second thing which is most
important is the warranty claim covered only,
you will get a claim only on the manufacturing company, for example,
if you see, the battery is not
manufactured by the company, and the tyre is
This company does not manufacture C8 or MRF, so
you will not get a claim on these things. You will get a claim only on the
company which is manufacturing it. For
example, look at the engine, there is a halogen
bulb and with it there is a fuel tank, there is a
clutch wire, whatever is related to this,
you will get a claim on the same things which the manufacturing company does. Along
with this, know the lifestyle,
lifestyle is three months and riding is
six months, from which date you will get to
count it, there are other
things also present in it, you should
read it as per your convenience, then you will
understand it. Let me tell you its online process,
how we apply for the claim,
after that whether the claim is approved or disapproved,
you will receive it on email. Here I am going to
tell you the process of online warranty claim, note one thing, if you want a separate video of the
product which is coming under your warranty claim, then
I will give you a list of which
warranty  It comes under the claim, why it does
not come, for this you
can ask by commenting below, number one scan QR code,
I will give you the QR code,
you have to scan that QR code, after scanning
you have to create an account here,
I will explain how to create it further,
after that you have to log in,
after logging in you have to claim your warranty,
as soon as you make the claim,
you have to fill some details like
name details etc. Once done,
I will explain all these things to you further, after that you will
receive an acknowledgement email, it is
clearly written in it whether your warranty claim is
approved or disapproved,
you will get to see all these things in it, so
let me explain the process to you in detail
through QR code, so first of all, take a screenshot of the
QR code which is in front of you here, take a
screenshot of it and keep it somewhere,
okay, now as soon as you scan this QR code,
you will go to this page,
here you have to create some account of yours, like
you can enter your name, last name, email
ID, mobile number, email ID, mobile number here, the email ID is
important, this is how you will login
Okay, after this enter the date of birth
and fill the gender here, as
you will create the account by filling these details,
after the account is created you have to login
in the login you have to enter the email id mobile number
which you had just created,
after this you will log in here with the password as
soon as you login you will see the next
process that you will see,
you can claim the warranty from here in this way,
two methods will be available in front of you all,
first through these nine dots, second
by clicking on this warranty claim, so
what you can do here by clicking on this, you can
claim the warranty, after that
you have to fill some details in which there is your name,
last name, email id, mobile number,
date of purchase is important, you
can see it in your invoice, in the papers you will get of the
bike you will see the date of purchase,
after that you will see the order id and the
code of the part, which is which part, what is
its code, after that you
can tell in details what
problems you are facing, if you have
its photos then you can also attach the
photos here  You can, after this you click on submit, as
soon as you click on submit,
you will
receive an acknowledgment email of warranty claim here
and it is written in it that within seven days
you will be told whether
your item is approved or
disapproved, you
can see all these things within seven days, if you want to get
more videos of any such warranty claim then
you can ask by commenting below,
I will make a separate video for it and
give it to you, if you like the video then like the video, to
see more such videos please subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon.
[Music]